

EHTEMAMUL HAQ MITUL

Residence -House#07,Road#01,Zinzira, Keranigong,

Dhaka-1310, Bangladesh

Cell Phone #:+8801622870077 Email Address: mitulehtl892@gmail.com

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Results oriented with 3+ years experience in corporate sales ,Human Resource and with a demonstrated history of working in the healthcare and Media industry.My goal is to become associated with a company where I can utilize my skills and gain further experience while enhancing the company's productivity and reputation. Moreover, I am an honest,hardworking person with a positive attitude in pursuit of knowledge and experience to establish my career.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Ensures Accountability | Networks Building | Sales and Collection Forecasting | Project Management | Relationship Building | Operations Management | Business Process Improvement | Vendor Management | Agile and Scrum | Management, and Business Development | Administrative Skills | Problem Solving | Market Analysis | Multitasking | Strong organization and Communication Skills | Experience with Employee Onboarding, Training, and Out-Processing | Teamwork | Finance Knowledge | Analytically Driven and Oriented.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Doctorkoi (A Concern of Renssoft Solutions Limited)

Oct 2020 - Present

Position : Assistant Manager, Corporate Sales & Vendor Management. Key Deliverables

- Work closely with the sales team to generate more field leads.
- Continuously approach new pharma management with the contracts and generate sales leads.
- Land Pharma business contracts via the management.
- Work Closely with the product team to generate an Operation Panel where all the results in the company are compiled.

- Prepares reports for existing clients (pharmaceuticals company) by collecting data, analyzing, and summarizing information.
- Work closely with the accounts department.
- Involvements with vat,tax,Legal of the company.
- Work closely with the management upon given tasks.
- Involvement with compliance related work as per management given task.
- Manage the Stakeholders of the company.
- Forecast sales growth and degrowth.
- Management reporting on a weekly and monthly basis.

Position : Senior Executive, HR & Admin Key Deliverables

Jun 2019 - Sep 2020

- Maintain the attendance in the Attendance sheet (Including leaves and delays).
- Collect advance recruitment requirements from team leads and post to the various sites.
- Keep a track of leave takers on a daily basis on the attendance management sheet/leave tracker and prepare reports to management on a weekly basis.
- Full planning and organizational activities to host the training sessions.
- Prepare salary after making all the adjustments with TADA and deductions in payroll. Prepare salary slip for every employee.
- Manage the monthly performance measurement of each and every payroll employee.
- Manage the employee requirements. Generate quotation for management to authorize, collect the money and purchase the amount/pay the bill. Send a report to management on a weekly basis.
- Manage the Stakeholders of the company.
- Manage and organize the employee database,
- Manage the partners and vendors.
- Involvement with compliance related work as per management given task.
- Management reporting on a weekly and monthly basis.

City FM 96 (Media City Limited)

Jun 2018 - Mar 2019

Position : Corporate Sales Executive Key Deliverables

- Analyzing competitors' products to determine product features, benefits, shortfalls, and market success.
- Calling potential customers to explain company products and encourage purchases.
- Developing and sustaining long-lasting relationships with the companies.
- Research and analyze sales options.
- Visit different companies everydays and promote the product.

- Prepare and submit the bills to the companies for selling the product.
- sells products by establishing contact and developing relationships.

EDUCATION

Lincoln University College, Malaysia

Bachelor (Hons) in Business Administration-2018
Thesis | The Impact of Distributional Channel Differentiation on
Organizational Performance
CGPA 2.73/4.00

Bir Shreshtha Munshi Abdur Rouf College.Pilkhana, Dhaka.

Higher Secondary certificate - 2012 Business Studies | GPA 4.00/5.00

Armanitola Govt High School, Dhaka.

School Secondary Certificate - 2010 Business Studies | GPA 4.38/5.00

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 6th March 1993.

Father's Name: Ehteshamul Hoque

Mother's Name: Mahbuba Khatun Rekha

Nationality: Bangladeshi.

INTERESTS

Following Business and Financial News | Reading Business and Financial Magazines | Traveling | Reading Books | Stamp Collecting | Going to the Gym.

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

Software: Ms-excel | Ms-word | Ms-powerpoint | Ms-outlook | Office 365 | SPSS.

Mini Project: Employee Onboarding process | Vendors onboarding process.

Reference: Available upon request.